{
    "subject": "resource/John_Hennessy_Saul",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_people_of_Irish_descent",
    "human_readable": "John Hennessy Saul is about American people of Irish descent.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9563660621643066,
            "question": "Is John Hennessy Saul of Irish origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9536399245262146,
            "question": "Does John Hennessy Saul's ancestry include Ireland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612926602363586,
            "question": "What is the ethnicity of John Hennessy Saul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551587462425232,
            "question": "To which American group does John Hennessy Saul belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7690787315368652,
            "question": "Where are John Hennessy Saul's ancestors from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6745992302894592,
            "question": "What nationality is John Hennessy Saul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.67083340883255,
            "question": "Can you tell me about John Hennessy Saul's ancestral roots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6323445439338684,
            "question": "What is John Hennessy Saul's heritage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5992953777313232,
            "question": "From which country did John Hennessy Saul's family originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5646089911460876,
            "question": "What cultural background does John Hennessy Saul come from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Hennessy Saul is about American people of Irish descent.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1310_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=From which country did John Hennessy Saul's family originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1310_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is John Hennessy Saul's heritage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1310_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about John Hennessy Saul's ancestral roots?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1310_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1310_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide significant information that supports the statement that John Hennessy Saul is about American people of Irish descent. Specifically, the text mentions his birth in County Cork, Ireland, and his emigration to the United States where he established a thriving horticultural business and worked on notable projects such as the National Mall in Washington, D.C., indicating his dual cultural heritage and professional success in America."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}